Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXXIX. RULES
  - Sub-Series 279-367. Rules. Santa Fe Tie and Lumber Preserving Company
    - Union Shop, 1951-1957 (Box 436, Folder 36)
    - General, 1945-1951 (Box 436, Folder 37)
    - Santa Fe Tie and Lumber Preserving Company, 1942-1944 (Box 436, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 279-368. Rules. Sioux City Terminal Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 436, Folder 39)
    - Sioux City Terminal Railway Company, 1951-1958 (Box 436, Folder 40)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 436, Folder 41)
    - General, 1942-1950 (Box 436, Folder 42)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1951 (Box 436, Folder 43)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 436, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 279-369. Rules. Ogden Union Stockyards Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 436, Folder 45)
    - General, 1942-1951 (Box 436, Folder 46)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 436, Folder 47)
    - Ogden Union Stockyards Company, 1942 (Box 437, Folder 1)
    - Ogden Union Stockyards Company, 1944-1947 (Box 437, Folder 2)
    - Ogden Union Stockyards Company, 1947 (Box 437, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 279-371. Rules. Southern Pacific Transport Company
    - Southern Pacific Transport Company, 1942-1945 (Box 437, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 279-372. Rules. Missouri-Illinois Railroad Company
    - 40 Hour Week, 1949-1958 (Box 437, Folder 5)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 437, Folder 6)
    - Missouri-Illinois Railroad Company, 1952-1953 (Box 437, Folder 7)
    - Missouri-Illinois Railroad Company, 1951-1952 (Box 437, Folder 8)
    - Missouri-Illinois Railroad Company, 1944-1950 (Box 437, Folder 9)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 437, Folder 10)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1949 (Box 437, Folder 11)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1942-1943 (Box 437, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-373. Rules. Salt Lake City Union Depot and Railroad Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 437, Folder 13)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 437, Folder 14)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 437, Folder 15)
    - Salt Lake City Union Depot and Railroad Company, 1949-1950 (Box 437, Folder 16)
    - Fred Harvey Service, Incorporated, 1942-1945 (Box 437, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-374. Rules. Fred Harvey Service, Incorporated
    - Union Shop, 1951-1957 (Box 437, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 279-375. Rules. New York Central Building
    - Mediation Case, 1958 (Box 437, Folder 19)
    - New York Central Building, 1942-1958 (Box 437, Folder 20)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 437, Folder 21)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 437, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 279-376. Rules. J.P. Carey and Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 437, Folder 23)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1952 (Box 437, Folder 24)
    - J.P. Carey and Company, 1942-1961 (Box 437, Folder 25)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 437, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 279-377. Rules. Yermo Freight Handlers, Incorporated
    - Yermo Freight Handlers, Incorporated, 1942 (Box 437, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 279-378. Rules. Pacific Motor Trucking Company
    - General, 1961-1962 (Box 438, Folder 1)
    - General, 1956-1961 (Box 438, Folder 2)
    - Pacific Motor Trucking Company, 1942-1955 (Box 438, Folder 3)
    - Pacific Motor Trucking Company, 1960-1961 (Box 438, Folder 4)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 438, Folder 5)
    - Pacific Motor Trucking Company, 1948-1952 (Box 438, Folder 6)
    - Vacations, 1946 (Box 438, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 279-379. Rules. Goldsboro Union Station Company
    - Union Shop, 1957 (Box 438, Folder 8)
    - Goldsboro Union Station Company, 1942-1943 (Box 438, Folder 9)
    - Goldsboro Union Station Company, 1948-1949 (Box 438, Folder 10)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 438, Folder 11)
    - Goldsboro Union Station Company, 1960-1961 (Box 438, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-380. Rules. Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company
    - Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company, 1962-1963 (Box 438, Folder 13)
    - Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company, 1956-1961 (Box 438, Folder 14)
    - Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company, 1949-1950 (Box 438, Folder 15)
    - Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company, 1947-1949 (Box 438, Folder 16)
    - Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company, 1946 (Box 438, Folder 17)
    - Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company, 1944-1945 (Box 438, Folder 18)
    - Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company, 1942-1943 (Box 438, Folder 19)
    - Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company, 1953-1955 (Box 438, Folder 20)
    - Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company, 1957-1958 (Box 438, Folder 21)
    - Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company, 1950-1953 (Box 438, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 279-381. Rules. Detroit and Mackinac Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 439, Folder 1)
    - Detroit and Mackinac Railway Company, 1943-1955 (Box 439, Folder 2)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 439, Folder 3)
    - Detroit and Mackinac Railway Company, 1943 (Box 439, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 279-382. Rules.
    - Shreveport Joint Car Inspection and Interchange Bureau, 1943-1946 (Box 439, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 279-383. Rules. Macon Terminal Company
    - Mediation Case, 1961-1967 (Box 439, Folder 6)
    - Macon Terminal Company, 1943-1954 (Box 439, Folder 7)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 439, Folder 8)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 439, Folder 9)
    - Macon Terminal Company, 1944-1945 (Box 439, Folder 10)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 439, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-384. Rules. T.F. Quinn and Company, Incorporated
    - T.F. Quinn and Company, Incorporated, 1943-1959 (Box 439, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-385. Rules. Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 439, Folder 13)
    - Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau, 1943-1952 (Box 439, Folder 14)
    - Rule 21, 1952 (Box 439, Folder 15)
    - Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau, 1953-1963 (Box 439, Folder 16)
    - Rule 43, 1950 (Box 439, Folder 17)
    - Southeastern Demurrage and Storage Bureau, 1943 (Box 439, Folder 18)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 439, Folder 19)
    - Vacations, 1944 (Box 439, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 279-386. Rules. William A. Smith Construction Company
    - William A. Smith Construction Company, 1943 (Box 439, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 279-387. Rules. American Refrigerator Transit
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 439, Folder 22)
    - American Refrigerator Transit, 1943-1950 (Box 439, Folder 23)
    - American Refrigerator Transit, 1943-1944 (Box 439, Folder 24)
    - American Refrigerator Transit, 1950-1952 (Box 439, Folder 25)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 439, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 279-388. Rules. Burlington Refrigerator Express
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 439, Folder 27)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 439, Folder 28)
    - Burlington Refrigerator Express, 1944-1945 (Box 439, Folder 29)
    - Burlington Refrigerator Express, 1943-1945 (Box 439, Folder 30)
    - Burlington Refrigerator Express, 1944 (Box 439, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 279-390. Rules. Philadelphia, Bethlehem, and New England Railroad Company
    - Mediation Case, 1962 (Box 439, Folder 32)
    - Philadelphia, Bethlehem, and New England Railroad Company, 1956-1962 (Box 439, Folder 33)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 439, Folder 34)
    - General, 1943-1955 (Box 440, Folder 1)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 440, Folder 2)
    - Case No. R-1103, 1943 (Box 440, Folder 3)
    - Case No. A-2406, 1945-1947 (Box 440, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 279-391. Rules. Chicago and Calumet River Railroad
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 440, Folder 5)
    - General, 1943-1959 (Box 440, Folder 6)
    - Case No. A-3550, 1950 (Box 440, Folder 7)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 440, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-392. Rules. Greenwich and Johnsonville Railroad
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1960 (Box 440, Folder 9)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1952 (Box 440, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 279-393. Rules. Texas City Terminal Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 440, Folder 11)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 440, Folder 12)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1952 (Box 440, Folder 13)
    - Case No. A-3834, 1951-1952 (Box 440, Folder 14)
    - Case No. R-1142, 1943-1944 (Box 440, Folder 15)
    - Case No. A-1567, 1943-1944 (Box 440, Folder 16)
    - General, 1944 (Box 440, Folder 17)
    - General, 1943-1944 (Box 440, Folder 18)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 440, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 279-394. Rules. Savannah and Atlanta Railway
    - Union Shop, 1951-1957 (Box 440, Folder 21)
    - General, 1943-1954 (Box 440, Folder 22)
    - Case No. R-1141, 1943-1944 (Box 440, Folder 23)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 440, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 279-395. Rules. Chicago Railroad Freight Collection Association
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 440, Folder 25)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 440, Folder 26)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1952 (Box 440, Folder 27)
    - Case No. R-1165 (Box 440, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 279-396. Rules. Wichita Terminal Association
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 441, Folder 1)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1958 (Box 441, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 279-397. Rules. Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 441, Folder 3)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 441, Folder 4)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 441, Folder 5)
    - Case No. A-2727, 1947-1948 (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 279-398. Rules. Southern Freight Tariff Bureau, Atlanta, Georgia
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 441, Folder 7)
    - Case No. R-1164, 1943 (Box 441, Folder 8)
    - General, 1943-1947 (Box 441, Folder 9)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 441, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 279-399. Rules. Joint Stockyards Agency, East St. Louis, Illinois
    - Case No. R-1259, 1943-1947 (Box 441, Folder 11)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 441, Folder 12)
    - General, 1945-1953 (Box 441, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 279-401. Rules. Atlanta and St. Andrews Bay Railway
    - Atlanta and St. Andrews Bay Railway, 1943-1955 (Box 441, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 279-403. Rules. Missouri Produce Yards, Kansas City, Missouri
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 441, Folder 15)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1958 (Box 441, Folder 16)
    - General, 1941-1950 (Box 441, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-404. Rules. Manistee and Northeastern Railway Company
    - General, 1955-1959 (Box 441, Folder 18)
    - Checkoff, Union Shop, 1958-1959 (Box 441, Folder 19)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 441, Folder 20)
    - General, 1943-1954 (Box 441, Folder 21)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 441, Folder 22)
    - Case No. A-2966, 1948-1949 (Box 441, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 279-405. Rules. Union Passenger Depot Company, Galveston, Texas
    - General, 1944-1959 (Box 441, Folder 24)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1957 (Box 441, Folder 25)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 441, Folder 26)
    - Case No. R-1262, 1944 (Box 441, Folder 27)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 441, Folder 28)
    - Case No. A-1937, 1944-1945 (Box 441, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 279-406. Rules. Rock Island Motor Transit Company
    - Rules Revision, 1959-1960 (Box 441, Folder 30)
    - General, 1951-1962 (Box 441, Folder 31)
    - General, 1944-1950 (Box 441, Folder 32)
    - Health and Welfare, 1956-1958 (Box 441, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 279-407. Rules. McKeesport Connecting Railroad
    - General, 1944-1952 (Box 441, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 279-408. Rules. Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad
    - Union Shop, 1951-1952 (Box 441, Folder 35)
    - General, 1944-1951 (Box 441, Folder 36)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 441, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 279-409. Rules. Joint Railway Agency, South St. Paul, Minnesota
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 441, Folder 38)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 441, Folder 39)
    - Case No. A-1792, 1943-1944 (Box 442, Folder 1)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 279-410. Rules. Chicago, Aurora, and Elgin Railroad Company
    - Chicago, Aurora, and Elgin Railroad Company, 1952-1961 (Box 442, Folder 3)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 442, Folder 4)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 442, Folder 5)
    - Mediation Case No. A-5510, 1957 (Box 442, Folder 6)
    - Mediation Case No. A-5214, 1956 (Box 442, Folder 7)
    - General, 1944-1951 (Box 442, Folder 8)
    - Case No. A-3877, 1952 (Box 442, Folder 9)
    - Case No. A-3844, 1951-1952 (Box 442, Folder 10)
    - Case No. A-2264, 1944-1952 (Box 442, Folder 11)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1951 (Box 442, Folder 12)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 442, Folder 13)
      1948-January 1951.
  - Sub-Series 279-411. Rules. Tremont and Gulf Railway Company
    - General, 1944-1960 (Box 442, Folder 14)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 442, Folder 15)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 442, Folder 16)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 442, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-412. Rules. Rio Grande Motor Way, Denver-Colorado Springs Motor Way, and Denver-Salt Lake Pacific Stages
    - General, 1954-1963 (Box 442, Folder 18)
    - General, 1944-1953 (Box 442, Folder 19)
    - NLRB Case No. 30-RC-1886, 1960-1962 (Box 442, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 279-413. Rules.
    - Trailways Bus Depot, St. Louis, Missouri, 1951-1959 (Box 442, Folder 21)
    - Rules Revision, 1952-1953 (Box 442, Folder 22)
    - General, 1944-1950 (Box 442, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 279-414. Rules. Winston-Salem Terminal Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 442, Folder 24)
    - Union Shop, 1957-1958 (Box 442, Folder 25)
    - 40-Hour Week -1949-1952 (Box 442, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 279-416. Rules. Pan American World Airways
    - Mediation Case No. R-3291. Weather Observers and Rawinsonde Operators, 1958 (Box 443, Folder 1)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6130, 1960-1961 (Box 443, Folder 2)
      June 1960-61.
    - Mediation Case No. A-6130, 1959-1960 (Box 443, Folder 3)
      1959-May 1960.
    - General, 1961-1962 (Box 443, Folder 4)
      April 4, 1961-62.
    - Mediation Case No. A-6857, 1962-1963 (Box 443, Folder 5)
    - Case No. A-3339, 1949-1950 (Box 443, Folder 6)
    - General, 1953-1961 (Box 443, Folder 7)
      December 1953-April 3, 1961.
    - Agreement, 1946 (Box 443, Folder 8)
    - Case No. R-1589, 1946 (Box 443, Folder 9)
    - Union Shop. Nordman, R.I., 1952-1953 (Box 443, Folder 10)
    - Union Shop. Cook, A.J., 1952-1954 (Box 443, Folder 11)
    - Guided Missile Base. Mediation Cases Nos, C-2654 and R-1589, 1957-1958 (Box 443, Folder 12)
    - Case No. R-1719, 1947 (Box 443, Folder 13)
      May-December 1947.
    - General, 1946 (Box 443, Folder 14)
      July-October 1946.
    - General, 1945-1946 (Box 443, Folder 15)
      October 1945-June 1946.
    - Case No. C-2756. Guided Missile Base. Medical Orderlies, 1958 (Box 444, Folder 1)
    - Agreement, 1946 (Box 444, Folder 2)
    - General, 1944-1945 (Box 444, Folder 3)
      1944-September 1945.
    - Agreements, 1946-1953 (Box 444, Folder 4)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1956 (Box 444, Folder 5)
    - Union Shop, 1946-1953 (Box 444, Folder 6)
    - Arbitration, Cook, A.J., 1954 (Box 444, Folder 7)
    - Court Case. Cook, A.J., 1952 (Box 444, Folder 8)
    - General, 1946-1947 (Box 444, Folder 9)
      11/1/1946-4/1/1947.
    - General, 1948-1949 (Box 444, Folder 10)
      1948-March 1949.
    - General, 1952-1953 (Box 444, Folder 11)
      July 1952-November 1953.
    - General, 1949-1952 (Box 444, Folder 12)
      April 1949-June 1952.
    - General, 1964-1965 (Box 444, Folder 13)
      October 21, 1964-August 13, 1965.
    - Mediation Case No. A-3367, 1963-1964 (Box 444, Folder 14)
    - Case No. R-1589, 1945-1946 (Box 444, Folder 15)
    - Emergency Board No. 128. Exhibits, 1956 (Box 445, Folder 1)
    - General, 1963-1964 (Box 445, Folder 2)
      1963-October 20, 1964.
    - Union Shop, 1957-1961 (Box 445, Folder 3)
    - United States District Court, 1960 (Box 445, Folder 4)
    - Emergency Board No. 128. Transcript, vol. 1, 1960 (Box 445, Folder 5)
      1960 March 29
    - Emergency Board No. 128. Transcript, vol. 2, 1960 (Box 445, Folder 6)
      1960 April 18
    - Emergency Board No. 128. Transcript, vol. 3, 1960 (Box 445, Folder 7)
      1960 April 19
    - Emergency Board No. 128. Transcript, vol. 4, 1960 (Box 445, Folder 8)
      1960 April 20
    - Employees' Exhibits, 1960 (Box 445, Folder 9)
      1960 April
    - Emergency Board No. 128. Report to the President, 1960 (Box 445, Folder 10)
      1960 June 2
    - United States District Court, United States Court of Appeals, 1960 (Box 445, Folder 11)
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 1, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 1)
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 2, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 2)
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 3, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 3)
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 4, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 4)
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 5, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 5)
      1960 April 21
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 6, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 6)
      1960 April 22
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 7, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 7)
      1960 April 25
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 8, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 8)
      1960 April 26
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 9, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 9)
      1960 April 27
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 10, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 10)
      1960 April 28
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 11a, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 11)
      1960 April 29
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 11b, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 12)
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 5, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 13)
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 6, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 14)
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 7, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 15)
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 8, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 16)
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 9, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 17)
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 10, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 18)
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 11a, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 19)
    - Emergency Board. Transcript. vol. 11b, 1960 (Box 446, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 279-418. Rules. Hudson and Manhattan Railroad
    - Case No. R-1457, 1945 (Box 446, Folder 21)
    - Case No. R-2128, 1949 (Box 446, Folder 22)
    - Cases Nos. R-2126, R-2127, R-2128, R-2144, 1949 (Box 446, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 279-419. Rules. Oakland Terminal Railway
    - General, 1945-1963 (Box 447, Folder 1)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 447, Folder 2)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1958 (Box 447, Folder 3)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 447, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 279-420. Rules. Northeast Airlines, Inc.
    - Case No. R-2705, 1953 (Box 447, Folder 5)
    - General, 1945-1953 (Box 447, Folder 6)
    - Cases Nos. R-1718, R-1720, R-1721, 1946-1947 (Box 447, Folder 7)
    - Case No. A-3652, 1951-1953 (Box 447, Folder 8)
    - Case No. A-2715, 1947-1948 (Box 447, Folder 9)
    - Representation Case No. R-1721, 1947 (Box 447, Folder 10)
    - Case No. A-2261, 1945-1946 (Box 447, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-421. Rules. Sand Springs Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 447, Folder 12)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1958 (Box 447, Folder 13)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1955 (Box 447, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 279-422. Rules. Transcontinental Bus System, Inc., Continental Dixie
    - General, 1946-1949 (Box 447, Folder 15)
    - General, 1945 (Box 447, Folder 16)
    - Agreement, 1945 (Box 447, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-423. Rules. Collingwood Terminals, Limited
    - General, 1945 (Box 447, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 279-424. Rules. Searle Grain Company, Limited, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada
    - General, 1945 (Box 447, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 279-425. Rules. Niagara, St. Catherine's, and Toronto Railway
    - General, 1947-1957 (Box 447, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 279-426. Rules. Union Bus Station of Oklahoma City, Inc.
    - General, 1955-1959 (Box 447, Folder 21)
    - General, 1951-1954 (Box 447, Folder 22)
    - General, 1947-1950 (Box 447, Folder 23)
    - General, 1946 (Box 447, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 279-427. Rules. Freight Forwarding Companies
    - General, 1946-1963 (Box 448, Folder 1)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 448, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 279-429. Rules. Springmeier Shipping Company, Inc.
    - NLRB Cases Nos. 2-RC-10995 and 2-RM-1100, 1960-1961 (Box 448, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 279-430. Rules. New York Central Railroad Company Grain Elevators
    - General, 1948-1950 (Box 448, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 279-436. Rules. Air Transport Industry
    - General, 1949-1954 (Box 448, Folder 5)
      March 16, 1949-54.
    - General, 1948-1949 (Box 448, Folder 6)
      1948-March 15, 1949.
    - NMB Case R-2139, 1949-1952 (Box 448, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 279-437. Rules. Northwest Airlines, Inc.
    - General, 1960-1962 (Box 448, Folder 8)
      May 1960-62.
    - Mediation Cases Nos. C-2104, R-2783, R-3345, and R-3559, 1959-1962 (Box 448, Folder 9)
      October 1959-62.
    - General, 1957-1960 (Box 448, Folder 10)
      1957-April 1960.
    - Cases Nos. C-2104, R-2783, and R-3345, 1953-1959 (Box 448, Folder 11)
      1953-September 1959.
    - NMB Case No. R-2107, 1949-1950 (Box 448, Folder 12)
    - General, 1948-1952 (Box 448, Folder 13)
      October 1948-January 1952.
    - Mediation Case No. A-6347, 1960-1962 (Box 448, Folder 14)
    - General, 1947-1948 (Box 448, Folder 15)
      March 1947-September 1948.
    - Rules Revision, 1952 (Box 449, Folder 1)
      February-December 1952.
    - General, 1952-1956 (Box 449, Folder 2)
      February 1952-56.
    - Case No. R-2357, 1951-1953 (Box 449, Folder 3)
      December 1951-April 1953.
    - General, 1946-1947 (Box 449, Folder 4)
      1946-February 1947.
    - Mediation Case No. A-5069, 1955-1956 (Box 449, Folder 5)
    - Cases Nos. C-2104 and R-2357, 1953-1958 (Box 449, Folder 6)
      May 1953-58.
    - Case No. A-4296, 1953 (Box 449, Folder 7)
    - Case No. R-2357, 1951 (Box 449, Folder 8)
      July 15, 1951-November 1951.
    - Case No. R-2357, 1950-1951 (Box 449, Folder 9)
      1950-July 14, 1951.
    - Case No. R-2257, 1950-1957 (Box 449, Folder 10)
    - Case No. A-4201, 1953-1956 (Box 449, Folder 11)
    - Case No. A-3898, 1952 (Box 449, Folder 12)
    - Case No. R-2215, 1949-1950 (Box 449, Folder 13)
    - Case No. R-2107, 1949-1950 (Box 449, Folder 14)
    - Case No. A-2890, 1948 (Box 450, Folder 1)
    - Case No. R-1664, 1948-1949 (Box 450, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 279-438. Rules. Capital Airlines, Inc.
    - General, 1949-1959 (Box 450, Folder 3)
      July 1949-December 1959.
    - General, 1948-1949 (Box 450, Folder 4)
      July 1948-June 1949.
    - Agreement, 1952 (Box 450, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 279-438. Rules. Capital Airlines, Inc. and Pennsylvania Central Airline Corporation
    - General, 1946-1948 (Box 450, Folder 6)
      1946-June 1948.
    - Health and Welfare, 1957 (Box 450, Folder 7)
    - Case No. A-3723, 1951-1952 (Box 450, Folder 8)
    - National Mediation Board. United Transport Service Employees of America, CIO, 1948-1949 (Box 450, Folder 9)
    - Case No. C-2247, 1956 (Box 450, Folder 10)
    - Case No. A-6037, 1961 (Box 450, Folder 11)
    - Case No. C-2247, 1954 (Box 450, Folder 12)
    - Case No. C-2247. National Mediation Board. Transcript. vol. 1, 1956 (Box 450, Folder 13)
      1956 April 17
    - Case No. C-2247. National Mediation Board. Transcript. vol. 2, 1956 (Box 450, Folder 14)
      1956 April 18
    - Case No. C-2247. National Mediation Board. Exhibits, 1954 (Box 450, Folder 15)
    - Case No. R-1735, 1947 (Box 450, Folder 16)
      March 25, 1947-May 1947.
    - Case No. R-1735, 1947 (Box 450, Folder 17)
      1946-March 24, 1947.
    - Case No. A-2999, 1948-1949 (Box 450, Folder 18)
      October 1948-49.
  - Sub-Series 279-439. Rules. Eastern Airlines